buybluesteel.com 2015-10-06

# Privacy Policy | Blue Steel Jewelry, featuring Stainless Steel, Tungsten and Titanium Jewelry

BLUE STEEL is committed to ensuring that our customers’ personal privacy and information is protected. 

This privacy notice sets out how 'BLUE STEEL' uses and protects any information that you give us, when you use this website. 

Should we ask you to provide certain identifiable information to us when using this website, please be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement. 

BLUE STEEL may change this or update this policy in future. Please check this page occasionally to ensure that you are happy with any changes. This policy is effective from 07-23-2014. Continuing to use this site following any changes/modifications constitutes your acceptance of our updated information. 

### **What we collect** : 

We may collect the following information: 

  * name and job title 
  * contact information including email address 
  * demographic information such as zip code, preferences and interests 
  * to fulfill customer orders we collect and store your shipping/billing information and purchase data
  * other information relevant to customer surveys and/or offers 

### **  How do we use this information?**

This information helps us better understand your needs and allows us to provide you with better service. We also use it for the following reasons: 

  * internal record keeping 
  * order tracking
  * fraud prevention
  * website evaluation/data analysis
  * to improve our products and services 
  * periodically we may send promotional emails about new products, special offers or other information which we think you may find interesting using the email address you’ve provided and you are free to opt out of our mailing list at any time 
  * from time-to-time, we may also use your information to contact customers for market research purposes by email, phone, fax or mail, in order to better customize our website to reflect customer interests 

### **Security**

We are committed to ensuring that the information you provide is secure. In order to prevent unauthorized access or disclosure, we have appropriate physical, electronic and managerial procedures in place to safeguard all information we collect online. BLUE STEEL encrypts your personal information using industry standard GeoTrust SSL Certification.

### **Links to other websites**

Occasionally, our website may include links to other websites of interest. These links are provided for your convenience, but please note that we have no control or responsibility for the content of any linked websites. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information you provide when visiting linked sites and they are not governed by BLUE STEEL’s privacy notice. Please exercise due caution and read the privacy statement applicable to the website in question. 

### **Controlling your personal information**

You may choose to restrict the collection or use of your personal information in the following ways: 

  * when you are asked to fill in a form on our website, please look for and click on the box indicating that you do not want any information to be used by anybody for direct marketing purposes 
  * if you have previously agreed to us using your personal information for direct marketing purposes, you may change your mind at any time by emailing us at [customerservice@buybluesteel.com](mailto:customerservice@buybluesteel.com) or writing to us at: Blue Steel Jewelry, 26017 Huntington Lane Building C Valencia, CA 91355

We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission, or are required by law to do so. With your permission, we may use your personal information to send you promotional information about third parties which we think will be of interest to you. Likewise, if you are subscribed to our newsletter, we may send you promotional emails about Blue Steel or affiliated entities that we feel may be of interest to our subscribers.

You may request details concerning the personal information we store about you under the Data Protection Act of 1998. A small fee is applicable. Please contact us if you would like a copy of the information. 

If you believe that any information we have about you is incorrect or incomplete, please write to or email us as soon as possible at the address listed above. We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect. 

We appreciate your trust.
